{"sid": "XN8759LTMU4W_main", "calc_equals_delay": 0, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 352770, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 352772, "question": "23+37", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 359528]], "time_left_end": "294", "answered_time": 359528, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "294", "question_time_start": 359529, "question": "7+3+7+68", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 369953]], "time_left_end": "283", "answered_time": 369953, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "283", "question_time_start": 369954, "question": "76+47", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["calc_7", 372494], ["calc_6", 373261], ["calc_+", 374064], ["calc_4", 374976], ["calc_7", 375692], ["calc_=", 376575], ["submit", 380580]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "273", "answered_time": 380580, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "273", "question_time_start": 380580, "question": "4+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["calc_9", 391746], ["calc_8", 392380], ["calc_+", 393363], ["calc_1", 394063], ["calc_5", 394762], ["calc_=", 395728], ["submit", 400725]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "253", "answered_time": 400725, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "253", "question_time_start": 400726, "question": "3+79+88", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["calc_8", 406320], ["calc_8", 406570], ["calc_+", 407671], ["calc_8", 408370], ["calc_2", 409270], ["calc_=", 410086], ["submit", 414433]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "239", "answered_time": 414433, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "239", "question_time_start": 414433, "question": "3+7+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 419362]], "time_left_end": "234", "answered_time": 419362, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "234", "question_time_start": 419362, "question": "3+44+28", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["calc_4", 424044], ["calc_7", 424744], ["calc_+", 425493], ["calc_2", 426242], ["calc_8", 426960], ["calc_=", 427874], ["submit", 431621]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "222", "answered_time": 431621, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "222", "question_time_start": 431621, "question": "9+3+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 435785]], "time_left_end": "217", "answered_time": 435785, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "217", "question_time_start": 435785, "question": "16+786", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["calc_1", 438568], ["calc_6", 439300], ["calc_+", 439751], ["calc_7", 440550], ["calc_8", 441882], ["calc_6", 442732], ["calc_=", 443614], ["submit", 447046]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "206", "answered_time": 447046, "user_answer": "802", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "206", "question_time_start": 447047, "question": "6+4+27", "correct_answer": 37, "events": [["submit", 450243]], "time_left_end": "203", "answered_time": 450243, "user_answer": "37", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 450243, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "203", "question_time_start": 450244, "question": "6+8+8+97", "correct_answer": 119, "events": [["calc_9", 454890], ["calc_7", 455839], ["calc_+", 456623], ["calc_1", 457539], ["calc_6", 458289], ["calc_+", 459490], ["calc_6", 460343], ["calc_=", 461081], ["submit", 467226]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "186", "answered_time": 467226, "user_answer": "119", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "186", "question_time_start": 467226, "question": "8+7+8+63", "correct_answer": 86, "events": [["submit", 474069]], "time_left_end": "179", "answered_time": 474069, "user_answer": "86", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "179", "question_time_start": 474070, "question": "3+8+76", "correct_answer": 87, "events": [["submit", 482061]], "time_left_end": "171", "answered_time": 482061, "user_answer": "87", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "171", "question_time_start": 482061, "question": "89+58", "correct_answer": 147, "events": [["calc_8", 484292], ["calc_9", 484923], ["calc_+", 485727], ["calc_5", 486342], ["calc_8", 487425], ["calc_=", 488279], ["submit", 492055]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "161", "answered_time": 492055, "user_answer": "147", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "161", "question_time_start": 492055, "question": "24+16", "correct_answer": 40, "events": [["submit", 495553]], "time_left_end": "158", "answered_time": 495553, "user_answer": "40", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "158", "question_time_start": 495553, "question": "7+28+18", "correct_answer": 53, "events": [["calc_7", 497792], ["calc_+", 499404], ["calc_2", 500231], ["calc_8", 501167], ["calc_+", 502135], ["calc_1", 503129], ["calc_8", 504006], ["calc_=", 504830], ["submit", 508204]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "145", "answered_time": 508204, "user_answer": "53", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "145", "question_time_start": 508204, "question": "47+938", "correct_answer": 985, "events": [["calc_4", 510909], ["calc_7", 511540], ["calc_+", 512558], ["calc_9", 513547], ["calc_3", 514271], ["calc_8", 515024], ["calc_=", 516056], ["submit", 520576]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 520576, "user_answer": "985", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 520576, "question": "4+63+17", "correct_answer": 84, "events": [["submit", 528412]], "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 528412, "user_answer": "84", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 528412, "question": "4+6+9+77", "correct_answer": 96, "events": [["submit", 537208]], "time_left_end": "116", "answered_time": 537207, "user_answer": "96", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "116", "question_time_start": 537208, "question": "9+8+34", "correct_answer": 51, "events": [["calc_1", 541562], ["calc_7", 542278], ["calc_+", 543096], ["calc_3", 543654], ["calc_4", 544336], ["calc_=", 545046], ["submit", 548900]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "104", "answered_time": 548900, "user_answer": "51", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 548901, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "104", "question_time_start": 548901, "question": "46+89", "correct_answer": 135, "events": [["calc_4", 550701], ["calc_6", 551299], ["calc_+", 552006], ["calc_8", 552975], ["calc_9", 553368], ["calc_=", 554156], ["submit", 558827]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "94", "answered_time": 558827, "user_answer": "135", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "94", "question_time_start": 558827, "question": "29+66", "correct_answer": 95, "events": [["submit", 566688]], "time_left_end": "87", "answered_time": 566688, "user_answer": "95", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "87", "question_time_start": 566688, "question": "33+656", "correct_answer": 689, "events": [["submit", 574331]], "time_left_end": "79", "answered_time": 574331, "user_answer": "689", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "79", "question_time_start": 574332, "question": "6+7+6+87", "correct_answer": 106, "events": [["calc_1", 580661], ["calc_1", 580961], ["calc_+", 583060], ["calc_8", 583810], ["calc_+", 584791], ["calc_8", 585725], ["calc_7", 586907], ["calc_=", 587792], ["submit", 590890]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "63", "answered_time": 590890, "user_answer": "106", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "63", "question_time_start": 590890, "question": "7+19+24", "correct_answer": 50, "events": [["calc_2", 596103], ["submit", 600264]], "time_left_end": "53", "answered_time": 600264, "user_answer": "50", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "53", "question_time_start": 600265, "question": "3+9+9+16", "correct_answer": 37, "events": [["submit", 609910]], "time_left_end": "43", "answered_time": 609910, "user_answer": "37", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "43", "question_time_start": 609910, "question": "4+9+96", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 615657]], "time_left_end": "38", "answered_time": 615657, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "38", "question_time_start": 615657, "question": "9+8+7+77", "correct_answer": 101, "events": [["calc_1", 626065], ["calc_7", 627349], ["calc_+", 628181], ["calc_7", 629049], ["calc_+", 629730], ["calc_7", 630581], ["calc_7", 630747], ["calc_=", 631579], ["submit", 635043]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "18", "answered_time": 635043, "user_answer": "101", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "18", "question_time_start": 635044, "question": "9+47+74", "correct_answer": 130, "events": [["calc_9", 637609], ["calc_+", 638208], ["calc_4", 638992], ["calc_7", 639559], ["calc_+", 640674], ["calc_7", 641490], ["calc_4", 642090], ["calc_=", 643007], ["submit", 647293]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "6", "answered_time": 647293, "user_answer": "130", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "6", "question_time_start": 647294, "question": "6+6+36", "correct_answer": 48, "events": [["submit", 651768]], "time_left_end": "2", "answered_time": 651768, "user_answer": "48", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 651768, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "2", "question_time_start": 651768, "question": "4+4+59", "correct_answer": 67, "events": []}}}}}